Guide to the Service Employees International Union Local 585 Records, 1966-1989 AIS.1982.14
ULS Archives & Special Collections
- Chapter Files: Education, I.
  - School Districts, 1.
    - Cranberry School District - Negotiations, January-April 1974 (Box 6, Folder 28)
    - Cranberry School District - Negotiations, May-July 1974 (Box 6, Folder 29)
    - Cranberry School District - Contract Ratification Ballots, 1974 (Box 6, Folder 30)
    - Cranberry School District - Grievances (Box 6, Folder 31)
    - Cranberry School District - Job Posting, 1977-1978 (Box 6, Folder 32)
    - Cranberry School District - Seniority Lists, 1976-1979 (Box 6, Folder 33)
    - Cranberry School District - Contracts, 1977 (Box 6, Folder 34)
    - Cranberry School District - Negotiations, 1977 (Box 6, Folder 35)
    - Cranberry School District - Disciplines/Complaints, 1977-1979 (Box 6, Folder 36)
    - Cranberry School District - Chapter Internal, 1975-1976 (Box 6, Folder 37)
    - Deer Lakes School District - Organization, 1969 (Box 6, Folder 38)
    - Deer Lakes School District - Directory, 1970 (Box 6, Folder 39)
    - Deer Lakes School District - Subcontracting, 1970 (Box 6, Folder 40)
    - Deer Lakes School District - Job Posting/Schedules, 1971-1972 (Box 6, Folder 41)
    - Deer Lakes School District - Job Posting/Schedules, 1973 (Box 6, Folder 42)
    - Deer Lakes School District - Dues, 1971-1973 (Box 6, Folder 43)
    - Deer Lakes School District - Factionalism, 1971-1974 (Box 6, Folder 44)
    - Deer Lakes School District - Disciplines, Recommendations, 1970-1973 (Box 6, Folder 45)
    - Deer Lakes School District - Negotiations, 1969-1973 (Box 6, Folder 46)
    - Deer Lakes School District - Organization, 1969 (Box 6, Folder 47)
    - Deer Lakes School District - Negotiations, 1972-1973 (Box 6, Folder 48)
    - Deer Lakes School District - Union Rivalry: Teamsters, 1973 (Box 6, Folder 49)
    - Deer Lakes School District - Sub-Contracting, 1971 (Box 6, Folder 50)
    - Deer Lakes School District - Grievances/Arbitrations, 1970-1971 (Box 6, Folder 51)
    - Deer Lakes School District - Proposed Contract, 1969 (Box 6, Folder 52)
    - Deer Lakes School District - Proposed Contract, 1970 (Box 6, Folder 53)
    - Deer Lakes School District - Contract, 1970 (Box 6, Folder 54)
    - Deer Lakes School District - Contract, 1973 (Box 6, Folder 55)
    - Deer Lakes School District - Job Descriptions (Box 6, Folder 56)
    - Deer Lakes School District - Negotiations, 1973-1976 (Box 6, Folder 57)
    - Deer Lakes School District - Negotiations, 1975 (Box 6, Folder 58)
    - Deer Lakes School District - Scheduling (Box 6, Folder 59)
    - Deer Lakes School District - Seniority/Layoffs, 1973-1975 (Box 6, Folder 60)
    - Deer Lakes School District - Wage Re-Opener, 1974 (Box 6, Folder 61)
    - Deer Lakes School District - Discipline, 1974 (Box 6, Folder 62)
    - Deer Lakes School District - Grievances, 1974 (Box 6, Folder 63)
    - Deer Lakes School District - Sex Discrimination Suit, 1974 (Box 6, Folder 64)
    - Deer Lakes School District - Chapter Internal, 1974 (Box 6, Folder 65)
    - Deer Lakes School District - Seniority/Job Posting/Scheduling (Box 6, Folder 66)
    - Deer Lakes School District - Administration Personnel (Box 6, Folder 67)
    - Deer Lakes School District - Contracts, 1975 (Box 6, Folder 68)
    - Deer Lakes School District - Contracts, 1978 (Box 6, Folder 69)
    - Deer Lakes School District - Wage Settlement, 1977 (Box 6, Folder 70)
    - Deer Lakes School District - Negotiations, 1977 (Box 6, Folder 71)
    - Deer Lakes School District - Negotiations, 1978 (Box 6, Folder 72)
    - Deer Lakes School District - Seniority/Salary, 1978 (Box 6, Folder 73)
    - Deer Lakes School District - Sex Discrimination Case, 1973-1978 (Box 6, Folder 74)
    - Deer Lakes School District - Negotiations, 1975 (Box 6, Folder 75)
    - Deer Lakes School District - Seniority, 1976-1977 (Box 6, Folder 76)
    - Deer Lakes School District - Dues, 1975 (Box 6, Folder 77)
    - Deer Lakes School District - Chapter Internal, 1973-1978 (Box 6, Folder 78)
    - DuBios School District - Job Description/Structure, 1969-1971 (Box 6, Folder 79)
    - DuBios School District - Seniority Lists, 1970-1973 (Box 6, Folder 80)
    - DuBios School District - Negotiations, 1971 (Box 6, Folder 81)
    - DuBios School District - Contracts, 1971 (Box 6, Folder 82)
    - DuBios School District - Seniority Vote, 1977 (Box 6, Folder 83)
    - DuBios School District - School Directory, 1975 (Box 6, Folder 84)
    - DuBios School District - Sympathy Strike, 1975 (Box 6, Folder 85)
    - DuBios School District - Contracts, 1973 (Box 6, Folder 86)
    - DuBios School District - June Negotiations Proposal, 1975 (Box 6, Folder 87)
    - DuBios School District - Negotiations Proposal, 1975 (Box 6, Folder 88)
    - DuBios School District - Negotiations, 1974-1975 (Box 6, Folder 89)
    - DuBios School District - Organization, 1970-1971 (Box 6, Folder 90)
    - DuBios School District - Schedules, 1970-1972 (Box 6, Folder 91)
    - DuBios School District - Negotiations, 1970-1972 (Box 6, Folder 92)
    - DuBios School District - Dues, 1971-1973 (Box 6, Folder 93)
    - DuBios School District - Chapter Internal (Box 6, Folder 94)
    - DuBios School District - Job Structure/Descriptions (Box 6, Folder 95)
    - DuBios School District - Organization: Custodians, 1970-1971 (Box 6, Folder 96)
    - DuBios School District - Chapter Internal, 1971-1977 (Box 6, Folder 97)
    - DuBios School District - Negotiations, 1971-1975 (Box 6, Folder 98)
    - DuBios School District - Organization: Cafeteria, 1977 (Box 6, Folder 99)
    - DuBios School District - Contract Summary, 1975 (Box 6, Folder 100)
    - DuBios School District - Contract, 1975 (Box 6, Folder 101)
    - DuBios School District - Seniority Lists, 1976 (Box 6, Folder 102)
    - DuBios School District - Job Posting, 1976-1977 (Box 6, Folder 103)
    - DuBios School District - Negotiations, 1974-1977 (Box 6, Folder 104)
    - DuBios School District - Chapter Finances, 1974 (Box 6, Folder 105)
    - DuBios School District - Retirement Pension, 1974 (Box 6, Folder 106)
    - DuBios School District - Grievances, 1973 (Box 6, Folder 107)
    - DuBios School District - Seniority List, 1976 (Box 6, Folder 108)
    - DuBois School District - Contract Proposals, 1975 (Box 7, Folder 1)
    - DuBois School District - Negotiations, 1977 (Box 7, Folder 2)
    - DuBois School District - Francis Deitch Grievance, 1976 (Box 7, Folder 3)
    - DuBois School District - Membership List, 1976 (Box 7, Folder 4)
    - DuBois School District - Withdrawal Notices, 1977 (Box 7, Folder 5)
    - DuBois School District - Snow Day Grievance, 1977 (Box 7, Folder 6)
    - DuBois School District - Dues, 1974 (Box 7, Folder 7)
    - DuBois School District - Seniority Lists, 1976-1977 (Box 7, Folder 8)
    - DuBois School District - PSEA Raid, 1976-1977 (Box 7, Folder 9)
    - East Allegheny School District - Authorization Cards, 1969-1970 (Box 7, Folder 10)
    - East Allegheny School District - Organization, 1969-1971 (Box 7, Folder 11)
    - East Allegheny School District - Contracts, 1970 (Box 7, Folder 12)
    - East Allegheny School District - Negotiations, 1970-1972 (Box 7, Folder 13)
    - East Allegheny School District - Factionalism/Union Rivalry: NEA, 1970-1974 (Box 7, Folder 14)
    - East Allegheny School District - Strike, 1970 (Box 7, Folder 15)
    - East Allegheny School District - Grievances/Disciplines, 1970-1972 (Box 7, Folder 16)
    - East Allegheny School District - Job Postings/Duties, 1971-1972 (Box 7, Folder 17)
    - East Allegheny School District - Dues, 1970-1972 (Box 7, Folder 18)
    - East Allegheny School District - Dues Authorizations, 1970 (Box 7, Folder 19)
    - East Allegheny School District - Dues Authorizations, 1970 (Box 7, Folder 20)
    - East Allegheny School District - Negotiations, 1969-1970 (Box 7, Folder 21)
    - East Allegheny School District - Grievances/Disciplines, 1971 (Box 7, Folder 22)
    - East Allegheny School District - Work Roles, 1971 (Box 7, Folder 23)
    - East Allegheny School District - Union Rivalry: PSEA, 1972 (Box 7, Folder 24)
    - East Allegheny School District - Directory, 1972 (Box 7, Folder 25)
    - East Allegheny School District - Membership/Authorization Cards (Box 7, Folder 26)
    - East Allegheny School District - Union Rivalry: PSEA, 1974 (Box 7, Folder 27)
    - East Allegheny School District - Schedules/Salary/Seniority Lists, 1973 (Box 7, Folder 28)
    - Elizabeth Forward School District - Organization, 1967-1971 (Box 7, Folder 29)
    - Elizabeth Forward School District - Directory, 1970 (Box 7, Folder 30)
    - Elizabeth Forward School District - Dues, 1972-1973 (Box 7, Folder 31)
    - Elizabeth Forward School District - Wages/Scheduling/Unit Issue, 1968-1973 (Box 7, Folder 32)
    - Elizabeth Forward School District - Negotiations/Strikes, 1971-1973 (Box 7, Folder 33)
    - Elizabeth Forward School District - Contract, 1972 (Box 7, Folder 34)
    - Elizabeth Forward School District - Negotiations, 1971-1975 (Box 7, Folder 35)
    - Elizabeth Forward School District - Salary/Seniority Lists, 1972-1974 (Box 7, Folder 36)
    - Elizabeth Forward School District - Organization, 1971 (Box 7, Folder 37)
    - Elizabeth Forward School District - Negotiations, 1971-1973 (Box 7, Folder 38)
    - Elizabeth Forward School District - Union Rivalry, 1976 (Box 7, Folder 39)
    - Elizabeth Forward School District - Organization: Cafeteria, 1972-1974 (Box 7, Folder 40)
    - Elizabeth Forward School District - Directory, 1973 (Box 7, Folder 41)
    - Elizabeth Forward School District - Contracts, 1973 (Box 7, Folder 42)
    - Elizabeth Forward School District - Factionalism, 1974 (Box 7, Folder 43)
    - Elizabeth Forward School District - Grievances, 1974 (Box 7, Folder 44)
    - Elizabeth Forward School District - Seniority Bumping, 1974 (Box 7, Folder 45)
    - Elizabeth Forward School District - Meet and Discuss, 1974 (Box 7, Folder 46)
    - Elizabeth Forward School District - COLA, 1974 (Box 7, Folder 47)
    - Elizabeth Forward School District - Dues, 1974 (Box 7, Folder 48)
    - Elizabeth Forward School District - Organization: Cafeteria, 1974 (Box 7, Folder 49)
    - Elizabeth Forward School District - Negotiations, 1975 (Box 7, Folder 50)
    - Elizabeth Forward School District - Contracts: Cafeteria, 1975 (Box 7, Folder 51)
    - Elizabeth Forward School District - Subcontracting: Cafeteria, 1974 (Box 7, Folder 52)
    - Elizabeth Forward School District - Organization: Cafeteria, 1975 (Box 7, Folder 53)
    - Elizabeth Forward School District - Negotiations: Cafeteria, March-September 1975 (Box 7, Folder 54)
    - Elizabeth Forward School District - Negotiations: Cafeteria, 1975 (Box 7, Folder 55)
    - Elizabeth Forward School District - Negotiations/Union Rivalry: PSEA, 1975-1976 (Box 7, Folder 56)
    - Elizabeth Forward School District - Organization: Cafeteria, 1975 (Box 7, Folder 57)
    - Elizabeth Forward School District - Negotiations, 1975 (Box 7, Folder 58)
    - Elizabeth Forward School District - Dues, 1976 (Box 7, Folder 59)
    - Elizabeth Forward School District - Retroactive Pay, 1975 (Box 7, Folder 60)
    - Elizabeth Forward School District - Seniority/Union Membership, 1976 (Box 7, Folder 61)
    - Elizabeth Forward School District - Union Rivalry: PSEA, 1976 (Box 7, Folder 62)
    - Elizabeth Forward School District - Union Rivalry: PSEA, 1976 (Box 7, Folder 63)
    - Elizabeth Forward School District - Membership Cards, 1976 (Box 7, Folder 64)
    - Ellwood City School District - Organization, 1967-1968 (Box 7, Folder 65)
    - Ellwood City School District - Negotiations, 1973 (Box 7, Folder 66)
    - Ellwood City School District - Chapter Internal, 1973 (Box 7, Folder 67)
    - Ellwood City School District - Mackey Disciplines, 1973 (Box 7, Folder 68)
    - Ellwood City School District - Dues/Death Benefits, 1973 (Box 7, Folder 69)
    - Ellwood City School District - Organization, 1968 (Box 7, Folder 70)
    - Ellwood City School District - Organization, 1971 (Box 7, Folder 71)
    - Ellwood City School District - Negotiations, 1971-1975 (Box 7, Folder 72)
    - Ellwood City School District - Organization: Clerical, 1975 (Box 7, Folder 73)
    - Ellwood City School District - Job Posting, 1973 (Box 7, Folder 74)
    - Ellwood City School District - Grievances, 1969 (Box 7, Folder 75)
    - Ellwood City School District - Local 227 Transfer, 1969 (Box 7, Folder 76)
    - Ellwood City School District - Job Posting/Descriptions, 1969-1973 (Box 7, Folder 77)
    - Ellwood City School District - Meet and Discuss, 1973 (Box 7, Folder 78)
    - Ellwood City School District - Job Problems, 1973 (Box 7, Folder 79)
    - Ellwood City School District - Contracts: Custodial, 1971 (Box 7, Folder 80)
    - Ellwood City School District - Memorandum of Agreement, 1973 (Box 7, Folder 81)
    - Ellwood City School District - Contract: Custodial, 1973 (Box 7, Folder 82)
    - Ellwood City School District - Contracts: Cafeteria, 1971 (Box 7, Folder 83)
    - Ellwood City School District - Contracts: Cafeteria, 1973 (Box 7, Folder 84)
    - Ellwood City School District - Job Posting, 1974 (Box 7, Folder 85)
    - Ellwood City School District - Mackey Discipline, 1973-1974 (Box 7, Folder 86)
    - Ellwood City School District - Chapter Internal/Service, 1974 (Box 7, Folder 87)
    - Ellwood City School District - Authorization Cards: Clerical, 1974 (Box 7, Folder 88)
    - Ellwood City School District - Organization: Clerical, 1974 (Box 7, Folder 89)
    - Ellwood City School District - Fringe Benefits, 1974 (Box 7, Folder 90)
    - Ellwood City School District - Organization: Clerical, 1974-1975 (Box 7, Folder 91)
    - Ellwood City School District - Membership Campaign, 1975 (Box 7, Folder 92)
    - Ellwood City School District - Dombeck Grievance, 1974-1976 (Box 7, Folder 93)
    - Ellwood City School District - Negotiations, 1975-1976 (Box 7, Folder 94)
    - Ellwood City School District - Contract Ballots, 1976 (Box 7, Folder 95)
    - Ellwood City School District - School Board Policies, 1971 (Box 7, Folder 96)
    - Ellwood City School District - Contracts: Clerical, 1975 (Box 7, Folder 97)
    - Ellwood City School District - Job Descriptions (Box 7, Folder 98)
    - Ellwood City School District - Salary/Job Descriptions, 1974 (Box 7, Folder 99)
    - Ellwood City School District - Negotiations, April-December 1975 (Box 7, Folder 100)
    - Ellwood City School District - Negotiations, 1975-1976 (Box 7, Folder 101)
    - Ellwood City School District - Job Posting, 1974-1976 (Box 7, Folder 102)
    - Ellwood City School District - Clerical Contract Addendum, 1978 (Box 7, Folder 103)
    - Ellwood City School District - Contracts: Clerical, 1978 (Box 7, Folder 104)
    - Ellwood City School District - Contracts: Clerical, 1977 (Box 7, Folder 105)
    - Ellwood City School District - Clerical Contract Addendum, 1977 (Box 7, Folder 106)
    - Ellwood City School District - Job Descriptions: Clerical, 1971 (Box 7, Folder 107)
    - Ellwood City School District - Negotiations, 1978 (Box 7, Folder 108)
    - Ellwood City School District - Seniority, 1976 (Box 7, Folder 109)
    - Ellwood City School District - Chapter Officers, 1975 (Box 7, Folder 110)
    - Ellwood City School District - Contracts: Teachers: NEA, 1971 (Box 7, Folder 111)
    - Ellwood City School District - Contracts: Teachers: NEA, 1977 (Box 7, Folder 112)
    - Ellwood City School District - Salary/Seniority, 1976-1977 (Box 7, Folder 113)
    - Ellwood City School District - Negotiations, 1977-1978 (Box 7, Folder 114)
    - Ellwood City School District - Insurance Benefits, 1975-1977 (Box 7, Folder 115)
    - Ellwood City School District - Negotiations, 1975-1976 (Box 7, Folder 116)
    - Ellwood City School District - Wage Grievances, 1975 (Box 7, Folder 117)
    - Ellwood City School District - Contracts: Teachers: NEA, 1975 (Box 7, Folder 118)
    - Ellwood City School District - Proposed Contract, 1978 (Box 7, Folder 119)
    - Ellwood City School District - Negotiations, 1976-1978 (Box 7, Folder 120)
    - Ellwood City School District - Negotiations, June-July 1978 (Box 7, Folder 121)
    - Ellwood City School District - Negotiations, August 1978 (Box 7, Folder 122)
    - Ellwood City School District - Negotiations, September-October 1978 (Box 7, Folder 123)
    - Ellwood City School District - Contracts: Custodial, 1975 (Box 7, Folder 124)
    - Ellwood City School District - Contracts: Custodial, 1978 (Box 7, Folder 125)
    - Ellwood City School District - Contracts: Cafeteria, 1975 (Box 7, Folder 126)
    - Ellwood City School District - Contracts: Cafeteria, 1978 (Box 7, Folder 127)
    - Ellwood City School District - Cafeteria Contract Addendum, 1977 (Box 7, Folder 128)
    - Ellwood City School District - Salary/Seniority List, 1976 (Box 7, Folder 129)
    - Ellwood City School District - Organization: Clerical, 1975 (Box 7, Folder 130)
    - Ellwood City School District - Rose Ann Dunning Correspondence, 1977 (Box 7, Folder 131)
    - Ellwood City School District - Negotiations, 1975 (Box 7, Folder 132)
    - Ellwood City School District - Job Posting, 1976-1979 (Box 7, Folder 133)
    - Ellwood City School District - Miscellaneous (Box 7, Folder 134)
    - Fayette County Vo-Tech School District - Organization, 1978 (Box 8, Folder 1)
    - Fayette County Vo-Tech School District - Contracts, 1978 (Box 8, Folder 2)
    - Forest Hills School District - Organization, 1971 (Box 8, Folder 3)
    - Forest Hills School District - Discipline Cases, 1972-1973 (Box 8, Folder 4)
    - Forest Hills School District - Grievances/Disputes, 1972-1973 (Box 8, Folder 5)
    - Forest Hills School District - Negotiations, 1972 (Box 8, Folder 6)
    - Forest Hills School District - Dues, 1972-1973 (Box 8, Folder 7)
    - Forest Hills School District - Job Posting, 1973 (Box 8, Folder 8)
    - Forest Hills School District - Organization, 1971 (Box 8, Folder 9)
    - Forest Hills School District - Negotiations, 1972-1974 (Box 8, Folder 10)
    - Forest Hills School District - Contracts: Company Union, 1971 (Box 8, Folder 11)
    - Forest Hills School District - Contracts, 1972 (Box 8, Folder 12)
    - Forest Hills School District - Contracts, 1974 (Box 8, Folder 13)
    - Forest Hills School District - Negotiations, 1971-1976 (Box 8, Folder 14)
    - Forest Hills School District - Proposed Contract, 1972 (Box 8, Folder 15)
    - Forest Hills School District - Salary Lists, 1972-1974 (Box 8, Folder 16)
    - Forest Hills School District - Lay-Off Notices, 1976 (Box 8, Folder 17)
    - Forest Hills School District - Negotiations, 1974 (Box 8, Folder 18)
    - Forest Hills School District - Contracts, 1976 (Box 8, Folder 19)
    - Forest Hills School District - Contracts, 1978 (Box 8, Folder 20)
    - Forest Hills School District - Lay-Offs/Subcontracting, 1976-1978 (Box 8, Folder 21)
    - Forest Hills School District - Negotiations, 1975-1976 (Box 8, Folder 22)
    - Forest Hills School District - Discipline, 1975-1978 (Box 8, Folder 23)
    - Forest Hills School District - Selapack Withdrawal, 1978 (Box 8, Folder 24)
    - Forest Hills School District - Miscellaneous, 1973-1978 (Box 8, Folder 25)
    - Fox Chapel School District - Contracts: Company Union, 1971 (Box 8, Folder 26)
    - Fox Chapel School District - Dues/Membership, 1973 (Box 8, Folder 27)
    - Fox Chapel School District - Chapter Internal (Box 8, Folder 28)
    - Fox Chapel School District - Proposed Contract, 1973 (Box 8, Folder 29)
    - Fox Chapel School District - Organization, 1972-1973 (Box 8, Folder 30)
    - Fox Chapel School District - Negotiations, 1973 (Box 8, Folder 31)
    - Fox Chapel School District - Contracts, 1973 (Box 8, Folder 32)
    - Fox Chapel School District - Negotiations, 1976 (Box 8, Folder 33)
    - Fox Chapel School District - Dental Plan, 1973 (Box 8, Folder 34)
    - Fox Chapel School District - Krysinkski Transfer Grievance, 1976 (Box 8, Folder 35)
    - Fox Chapel School District - Contracts, 1976 (Box 8, Folder 36)
    - Fox Chapel School District - Employee List, 1976 (Box 8, Folder 37)
    - Fox Chapel School District - Negotiations, 1978 (Box 8, Folder 38)
    - Fox Chapel School District - Contracts, 1978 (Box 8, Folder 39)
    - Fox Chapel School District - Negotiations, 1974 (Box 8, Folder 40)
    - Fox Chapel School District - Negotiations, 1975-1976 (Box 8, Folder 41)
    - Fox Chapel School District - Miscellaneous, 1975-1979 (Box 8, Folder 42)
    - Franklin School District - Organization, 1970-1971 (Box 8, Folder 43-44)
    - Franklin School District - Organization, 1971 (Box 8, Folder 45)
    - Franklin School District - Contracts, 1971 (Box 8, Folder 46)
    - Franklin School District - Negotiations, 1971-1974 (Box 8, Folder 47)
    - Franklin School District - Negotiations, 1971-1972 (Box 8, Folder 48)
    - Franklin School District - Scheduling, 1972-1973 (Box 8, Folder 49)
    - Franklin School District - Building Security, 1973 (Box 8, Folder 50)
    - Franklin School District - Membership Cards/Dues, 1971-1973 (Box 8, Folder 51)
    - Franklin School District - Salary Schedule, 1970 (Box 8, Folder 52)
    - Franklin School District - Seniority Lists, 1971-1972 (Box 8, Folder 53)
    - Franklin School District - Job Descriptions, 1970 (Box 8, Folder 54)
    - Franklin School District - Grievance Arbitration, 1972 (Box 8, Folder 55)
    - Franklin School District - Proposed Contract, 1972 (Box 8, Folder 56-57)
    - Franklin School District - Contract, 1973 (Box 8, Folder 58)
    - Franklin School District - Job Bidding/Probation Periods, 1972-1973 (Box 8, Folder 59)
    - Franklin School District - Disciplines, 1972-1973 (Box 8, Folder 60)
    - Franklin School District - Dues, 1972-1973 (Box 8, Folder 61)
    - Franklin School District - Negotiations, 1972-1973 (Box 8, Folder 62)
    - Franklin School District - Contracts, 1974 (Box 8, Folder 63)
    - Franklin School District - Salary/Seniority List, 1973-1974 (Box 8, Folder 64)
    - Franklin School District - Job Requirements, 1970-1975 (Box 8, Folder 65)
    - Franklin School District - Wage Discrimination: Women, 1973-1974 (Box 8, Folder 66)
    - Franklin School District - Hiring/Job Assignments, 1974 (Box 8, Folder 67)
    - Franklin School District - Negotiations, 1972-1975 (Box 8, Folder 68)
    - Franklin School District - Contract Proposal, 1974 (Box 8, Folder 69)
    - Franklin School District - Board Proposal, 1974 (Box 8, Folder 70)
    - Franklin School District - Negotiations Notebook, 1975 (Box 8, Folder 71)
    - Franklin School District - Union Proposal, 1974 (Box 8, Folder 72)
    - Franklin School District - CETA Negotiations, 1974-1975 (Box 8, Folder 73)
    - Franklin School District - Health and Dental Plan, 1972-1975 (Box 8, Folder 74)
    - Franklin School District - Seniority, 1974 (Box 8, Folder 75)
    - Franklin School District - Negotiations, 1974-1975 (Box 8, Folder 76)
    - Franklin School District - Negotiations, 1975 (Box 8, Folder 77)
    - Franklin School District - Contracts, 1975 (Box 8, Folder 78)
    - Franklin School District - Dues, 1978 (Box 8, Folder 79)
    - Franklin School District - Chapter Internal, 1978 (Box 8, Folder 80)
    - Franklin School District - Mandatory Retirements, 1976-1977 (Box 8, Folder 81)
    - Franklin School District - Erb Suspension Grievance, 1975 (Box 8, Folder 82)
    - Franklin School District - Disciplines, 1975-1978 (Box 8, Folder 83)
    - Franklin School District - Scheduling/Promotions/Hiring, 1975-1978 (Box 8, Folder 84)
    - Franklin School District - Salary/Seniority Lists, 1971-1978 (Box 8, Folder 85)
    - Franklin School District - Negotiations, 1975-1979 (Box 8, Folder 86)
    - Franklin School District - Personnel Directory, 1973 (Box 8, Folder 87)